When I dress I don't think so much
I could be the GOAT
I don't need too much
I'mma set a goal
I'mma eat that lunch
Baby so cold get that ice cream truck
Uh 찌릿찌릿, 끼리끼리 놀아볼까?
kitty kitty yeah we gonna
run this town
Hittin' me up cause I
got what they like
Baby got no chance better
hit that dance
Mmm, na-na-na
I'll be there  고민하지 마
Uh, na-na-na
I'll be there  망설이지 마
But you don't know 'bout me
Yeah yeah, you gon' know 'bout me boy
아름다운 별들이 빛나는 밤이야
Mmmh, what you say
끝없는 가치
You know it's all me
Got that
Ooh, what you say
Are you ready?
Set, turn on the lights
Baby got passion, ambition
난 보란 듯이
Look at that
온몸으로 느끼는 내 몸짓
Baby got
Drip, drip, drip, drip,
drip, drip, drip
Baby got
Drip, drip, drip, drip,
drip, drip, drip
Let 'em out
Monster, monster, monster
came to conquer
Baby, holla wassup
We the best, the rest
confess, we blessed
판을 180도 바꿔 (바꿔)
Y to the G, no copy, no Knock off
Bet on my life
this pitch I'm gon' walk-off
MONSTIEZ 꽉 잡아 hold tight
끝까지 밟아
You know we gon' ride
Mmm, na-na-na
I'll be there 고민하지 마
Uh, na-na-na
I'll be there 망설이지 마
But you don't know 'bout me
Yeah yeah, you gon' know ‘bout me boy
아름다운 별들이 빛나는 밤이야
Mmmh, what you say
Endless worth
You know it's all me
Got that
Ooh, what you say
Are you ready?
Set, turn on the lights
Baby got passion, ambition
난 보란 듯이
Look at that
온몸으로 느끼는 내 몸짓
Baby got
Drip, drip, drip, drip,
drip, drip, drip
Baby got
Drip, drip, drip, drip,
drip, drip, drip
가끔 쓰러진대도
I'mma shine as bright as diamonds
Say my name
Get back up
Now watch me do it all again
Baby got drip, drip, drip
Baby got, baby got, baby got
Drip, drip, drip
You know we got got that drip
Baby got drip, drip, drip
Baby got, baby got, baby got
Drip, drip, drip
Got that drip yeah